Oleksii Nieznakomov | Front-End Developer



in LinkedIn | O LyoLik1 | Iyosha.neznakomov@gmail.com | @ @LyoLikk

ABOUT ME

I'm a Front-End Developer with 2 years of experience, focused on creating efficient and user-friendly applications. I am ready to actively work in a team and learn new technologies in web development. My goal is to achieve high results and make a significant contribution to the success of the company. Open to relocation for the right opportunity.

SKILLS

- Front-End Technologies: HTML, CSS, SASS, SCSS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Material UI, Emotion, Zustand, TanStack Query, Recharts, QR Scanner, GSAP, Swiper, React Hook Form, Three.js.
- Tools and Platforms: WebPack, Vite, Babel, npm, yarn, Netlify, Jest, i18n, Docker, WebSockets
- Other Skills: SQL, UI/UX design, SEO optimization, performance optimization, API integration, Email template, Feature-Sliced Design (FSD) Architecture, Atomic design.
- Languages: English, Ukrainian, Russian Professional proficiency or above. German in the learning process

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

<u>Viand Solar</u>

Front-End Developer

March 2024 - June 2024

- Developed a responsive and visually appealing informational website for showcasing solar panel solutions.
- Implemented SEO best practices to enhance online visibility and performance optimization techniques for improved site responsiveness.
- Stack: React, TypeScript, SASS, MUI, React Hook Form, GSAP, Swiper.

<u>News+Letter</u> Germany, remote

Front-End Developer 2024

March 2024 - August

- Contributed to the platform for curating and delivering personalized news content via email.
- Key responsibilities included implementing features and enhancements to improve user engagement and platform functionality.
- Stack: React, TypeScript, Vite, SASS, MUI, VanillaJS, GSAP, React Email.

Surroundly
Front-End Developer
October 2023 - Current

- Chat development using React, TypeScript, Zustand, React-Query and other tools.
- Integrated various APIs to enhance chat features.
- Create and maintain a responsive user interface with a strong emphasis on high performance and SEO in mind.
- Effectively manage project code using the Git version control system.
- Stack: React, TypeScript, Zustand, React Hook Form, yup, React-Query, Vite, Reacharts, WebSockets, QR Scanner.

EDUCATION

National University Odessa Polytechnic

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering

Ukraine, Odessa 2022 – current

Ukraine, Odessa 2020 - 2022